Bum bi-num bi-num bum bum bum bum bum bum bi-num bum bi-num bum bi-num bum bi-num bum bi-num bum bum bum bum bum
F***
该死
You are black
你是黑人
Nope
不是
No, mom
不，妈
I need to use my phone for streaming
我需要用手机直播
Mom, no
妈，不要
I need my phone to see the chat
我需要用手机看聊天室
My mom wants to use my phone
我妈想用我的手机
To look at her boyfriend
来看她的男朋友
My mom just wants to borrow my phone
我妈只是想借用我的手机
But I can't because I'm using it to be able to see chat
但我不能，因为我正用着它来看聊天室
While I'm gaming
当我玩游戏的时候
I will explain in Chinese so it's not heard
我会用中文解释，这样就不会被听到了
Hello
哈喽
She wants to use my phone to secretly look at her boyfriend
她想用我的手机偷偷看她的男朋友
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
I'll say it again
我再说一遍
She wants to use my phone to secretly look at her boyfriend
她想用我的手机偷偷看她的男朋友
Boyfriend?
男朋友？
Do you understand?
明白了吗？
Boyfriend?
男朋友？
Shoo
走开
Shoo shoo shoo
走开，走开，走开
Mom, please
妈，求你了
No
不
Mom, they can hear you, mom
妈，他们能听到你呀，妈
Come on!
拜托！
They can hear you, mom
他们能听到你，妈
No, mom.
不，妈。
Mom, please
妈，求你了
Okay, that's fine
好吧，没关系
Shut the door, please
请把门关上
I need to
我需要...
Oh, my gosh
天呐
I got distracted
我走神了
Yeah
嗯
I won't be able to read comments in a while
我一会儿没法看评论了
That's all
就这样
I won't be able to re-comment
我没法再评论了
What? What the fuck?
什么？这他妈的是怎么回事？
What the fuck?
这他妈的？
My mom's not taking my phone
我妈没拿走我的手机
She just wants to use my phone to...
她只是想用我的手机去...
To be able to...
为了能够...
Stalk
监视
I don't know
我不知道
See what's going on I guess
我想是想看看发生了什么
On...
在...
With her boyfriend
和她的男朋友
Because my mom is...
因为我妈是...
Yandere
病娇
But...
但是...
It's not good for me because I need to be able to see chat
这对我不太好，因为我需要看聊天内容
Well, great
额，真棒
Bye mom
拜拜，妈
Love you
爱你
Okay, love you
好啦，爱你
I got my phone back
我的手机拿回来了